videospinblasterpro.com 2019-06-04

# Blaster Marketing

****

**Privacy Policy**  
 **(Last Updated: May 25, 2018)**  

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from Blaster Suite Network. The Blaster Suite Websites are: http://blastersuite.com , http://liveblaster.com , http://liveblaster2.com , http://blastermarketing.com , http://videomarketingblasterpro.com , http://videomarketingblaster.com , http://pixoblaster.com , http://videoleadstudio.com , http://massvideoblasterpro.com , http://videospinblasterproplus.com , http://blasterbonus.com , http://lingoblaster.com . We will refer to this sites as the “Site”. This privacy policy will explain how our organization uses the personal data we collect from you when you use our website.

**What data do we collect?**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages from our website that you visit. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

**How do we collect your data?**

– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you enter your email, make a purchase, or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers and PayPal info), email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

**How do we use the your data?**  
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for delivery or shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, we use this Order Information to:  
Communicate with you;  
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.  
We also send relevant offers from our partners (affiliates) from time to time.  
We also use the info we collect about you on our site for advertising, retargeting, tracking sales, tracking actions across the site, etc…

**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Our website contains tracking pixels from Google and Facebook. We do not share your personal information (email, phone number) with anybody.For example, we use 2Checkout.com or JVzoo.com to power our online store–you can read more about how 2checkout.com uses your Personal Information here:  http://www.avangate.com/legal/privacy.php We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.  You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

**BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING**  
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

**You can opt out of targeted advertising by:**

FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads  
GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous  
BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/.

**DO NOT TRACK**  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

**YOUR RIGHTS**  
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

**DATA RETENTION**  
When you enter your email or place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Contact Information and Order Information for our records and marketing purposes unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

**CHANGES**  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

**CONTACT US**  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions or comments, please contact us support ticket at http://blastersuite.com/support
